http://www.titantv.com/privacy.aspx

Our
Terms of Service and our Privacy Policy have changed.
Please take a moment to review them.
By continuing to use our services, including our websites and mobile application,
you agree to our updated Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.
We use
and allow cookies to be stored on your device to improve user experience, analyze
usage, and assist in our marketing efforts.
We also share information about your
use with our advertising and analytics partners.
Favorite Shows & Movies  |
Current Reminders:
TIP No. 9
A setting in the Daily View Grid section Site Preferences/My Preferences tab allow you to specify whether the Daily View opens to display 3 or 14 days of programming by default.
View All
Contact TitanTV
Terms and Conditions of Use
Privacy Policy
Usage
Tips
TitanTV Mobile
Related Links
At TitanTV, Inc. (“TITANTV”, “we”,
“us” or “our”, herein),
we recognize the importance of privacy to users of our websites at
www.TitanTV.com
(“TitanTV.com”) and www.AntennaWeb.org (“AntennaWeb.org”),
and of the TitanTV.com
executable code version of the software provided by TITANTV (including associated
documentation and services) (the “TitanTV.com Mobile Application”,
and with the
services provided through the websites, collectively, the “Services”).
This privacy
policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains what type of information
may be collected from
you or that you may provide when you access the Services and how that information
may be used. Please note that this Privacy Policy pertains only to the Services,
and is separate and distinct from the privacy policies, end user license agreements,
terms or service, or terms of use governing: (a) the web sites, applications and
services of TITANTV's clients; (b) the web sites, applications and services that
may link to or from the Services; and (c) other TITANTV web sites, applications
or services.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices
regarding the information collected from you or that you may provide when you access
the Services and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and
practices, your choice is not to use the Services. By downloading, accessing or
using the Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may change
from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of the
Services after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please
check the Privacy Policy periodically for updates
1.	Information We Collect and How We Collect It.
We collect several types of information from and about users of the Services, including:
information by which you may be personally identified, such as username, email
address, location information, and any other identifier by which you may be contacted
online or offline (collectively, “personally-identifying information”);
information that is about you but individually does not identify you; and
information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access the
Services, and usage details.
We collect this information:
directly from you when you provide it to us;
automatically as you access and navigate the Services;
2.	Information You Provide Us.
You may be asked to provide personally-identifying information, such as your
username, email address, and other identifiers when you register for certain functions
and features included in the Services. TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application
provide the functionality for you to input a zip code to produce a tv channel line-up.
If you are using AntennaWeb.org, you may input a zip code as well as provide a street
level address to improve the accuracy of your results. You may also be asked to
provide personally-identifying information in other limited circumstances specified
at the time the information is gathered.
3.	Information Collected Automatically.
As you access and navigate the Services we may use automatic data collection technologies
to collect information about your equipment and actions on the Services. This information
allows TITANTV to improve the Services and make them more useful to our users. This
information may contain some or all of the following information:
The Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) of the device which downloaded, installed
or used the Services.
The date of use.
The time of use.
The path taken as you navigate through the Services.
The operating system and device type being used.
A list of files downloaded or viewed.
The amount of time spent listening to/viewing media files.
Any errors encountered.
The device’s geographic location.
3.1.	Cookies and Other Technologies.
TITANTV may also use 'cookies' to collect information. A cookie is a string of characters
that can be written to a file on the user's device when a user accesses the Services.
When accessing TitanTV.com or AntennaWeb.org, you may refuse to accept browser cookies
by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this
setting you may be unable to access certain parts of TitanTV.com or AntennaWeb.org.
TITANTV uses cookies to track users' activity through the Services so that we may
improve the Services, to provide certain features, to provide third party content,
and to recall specific information to save the user time during subsequent use of
the Services. For example, cookies allow TITANTV to remember your (and/or your device’s)
location. Interactive features may also use cookies. Our sponsorship service vendors,
which serve sponsorship messages onto TitanTV.com and the TitanTV.com Mobile Application,
and third party vendors that measure and analyze the use of TitanTV.com and the
TitanTV.com Mobile Application for TITANTV, may also use their own cookies.
TITANTV and the third party vendors may use web beacons, alone or in conjunction
with cookies, to measure and analyze use of Services. A web beacon is an electronic
image, also known as a single-pixel (1x1) or clear .gif, which can be used to recognize
certain information on your device, such as cookies, the time and date of your actions
within the Services, and a description of where content is placed.
4.	Use of Information
TITANTV may use information that we collect about you or that you provide us, including
personally-identifying information to:
present, manage or administer the Services and their contents;
optimize or customize the delivery of advertising or content to you and other users
of the Services;
to contact users and respond to user messages;
contact users about online surveys;
contact you, if you opt into such notifications, about future functionality of the
Services;
other internal TITANTV or TITANTV client purposes;
carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered
into between you and us;
notify you about changes to our Services or any products or services we offer or
provide though the Services;
for any purpose for which you provide it;
for other purposes specified at the time the information is gathered; and/or
for any other purpose with your consent.
5.	Disclosure of Information.
Personally-identifying information collected by TITANTV may be disclosed as described
in this Privacy Policy:
to TITANTV’s clients, suppliers, licensors, advertising partners, and service vendors;
to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring,
reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of TITANTV's
assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar
proceeding, in which personal information held by TITANTV about users of the Services
is among the assets transferred;
if required to do so by law or if TITANTV believes that such action is necessary
to comply with the law or with legal process including any government or regulatory
request;
if we believe disclosure is necessary to protect against misuse or unauthorized
use of the Services or to protect the personal safety or property of users of the
Services, the public or TITANTV and its employees;
for any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information; and
with your consent.
If you do not want your personally-identifying information to be collected or used
for any of these purposes, please do not provide it and do not access TitanTV.com,
AntennaWeb.org or download, install or use the TitanTV.com Mobile Application.
6.	Third-Party Advertising
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you access or use the
Services. Some of these third-party advertising companies may use information about
your visits to the Services and other websites in order to provide advertisements
on the Services and other web sites about goods and services that may be of interest
to you. We do not control third-party advertising companies' collection or use of
your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third-party
advertising companies may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information
collected or used in this way. If you would like more information about this practice
and to know your choices about not having this information used by some of these
third-party advertising companies, please click here.
7.	Security
TITANTV has implemented measures designed to secure your personally-identifying
information
from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.
However, no Internet, e-mail or mobile transmission is ever fully secure or error
free and TITANTV cannot guarantee that any information will be or remain safe or
secure. Because most e-mail and mobile transmissions are not encrypted, you should
take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail, SMS or
text message, or other mobile transmission. Any transmission of personally-identifying
information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any
privacy settings or security measures contained on the Services.
8.	California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional
rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your
California privacy rights, please see our California Privacy
Notice.
9.	Children
If you are under 13 years of age, please do not access TitanTV.com, AntennaWeb.org
or download, install or use the TitanTV.com Mobile Application. The Services are
not intended for children under 13, and TITANTV will not knowingly collect any information
from any children under the age of 13. If we discover that we have collected any
personally-identifying information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly
remove that information from our database. If you believe we might have any information
from or about a child under 13, please contact us at privacy@TitanTV.com.
10.	Do Not Track
The Services do not respond to do not track signals.
11.	Changes to the Privacy Policy.
TITANTV reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Any changes to this Privacy
Policy will be posted to this page, with a notice that this Privacy Policy has been
updated on the TitanTV.com and AntennaWeb.org home pages and a notification through
the TitanTV.com Mobile Application. Please check this page periodically. Use of
the Services constitutes consent to any policy then in effect. Please make sure
that you read the TitanTV Terms and Conditions
of Use
to understand additional terms
and conditions which apply to the use of the Services.
12.	Links to other Sites and Services
The Services may contain links to other sites, applications and services maintained
by third parties (collectively, “Third Party Services”)
that may not follow the
same privacy and data security practices as TITANTV. For example, clicking or tapping
on a sponsorship notice or some third party logos on the Services may take you to
Third Party Services with entirely different privacy and data security practices.
These Third Party Services are subject to their own privacy policies and terms and
conditions and may use cookies, collect data, and use the data in ways that TITANTV
would not. TITANTV is not responsible for the privacy and data security practices
or any information or materials on Third Party Services. Please review the Third
Party Services’ policies and terms and conditions for more information on how they
use your information.
In some cases, the Services may include certain embedded tools provided and controlled
by third parties and governed by the policies and terms and conditions of the third
parties providing such tools. You should only use these third party tools if you
agree to their respective policies and terms and conditions.
The Services may include a tool that allows you to share a link via Twitter or “Like”
certain portions of the Services. Please be aware that those Third Party Services
are unrelated to TITANTV, and that your use of the Third Party Services is subject
to the third party provider’s policies and terms and conditions of those services.
13.	International User Notice
For international users, please note that it may be necessary to transfer your information
internationally and, in particular, your information may be transferred to and processed
in the United States. For residents of the European Union: the data protection and
other laws of other countries outside of the European Union may not be as comprehensive
as those of the European Union. By downloading, accessing or using the Services
you agree to have your information transferred to, and used in, the United States
as set forth in this policy. If you download, access or use the Services from the
European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal
data collection, use and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please
be advised that through your continued use of the Services, which is governed by
U.S. law, this Privacy Policy and the TitanTV Terms
and Conditions of Use, you are
transferring your personally-identifying information to the United States and you
consent to that transfer and use.
14.	Questions
If you have any questions or comments concerning our Privacy Policy regarding TitanTV.com,
please contact us at privacy@TitanTV.com.
Copyright TitanTV, Inc. 2016      U.S. Patent No.
7,631,332
Loading, Please wait...
show bar
Tweet
